

I am highly motivated to find my first job as a front-end developer.
I have been studying web-development almost for one year. I have 4 projects done using modern web development technologies. I am definitely a team and hard worker.

CONTACT ME

- (063) 567 36 30
- irynailina@gmail.com
- Kyiv, Ukraine
- irynailina



TECH SKILLS

HTML5
CSS3
JAVASCRIPT
REACT
REDUX
NODE.JS (IN PROGRESS)
WEBPACK
REST API
GIT



SOFT SKILLS

AGILE
SCRUM
TEAMWORK
FAST LEARNER
PATIENT

IRYNA ILINA

FRONT-END DEVELOPER



PROJECTS

- https://katrusy86.github.io/G-B/build/
 Adaptive web-site for English language teacher
 Stack: HTML5, CSS3, Gulp
- https://puvel.github.io/Films_library
 Adaptive search movies application
 Stack: JavaScript, Webpack, REST API
- https://make-it-easy-questify.netlify.app
 Adaptive to-do list application
 Stack: React.js, Redux, REST API



WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior cabin crew member

June 2015 - Feb 2020 - Ukraine International Airlines

Providing safety and service on board Cabin crew management and control

Sales specialist

June 2014- June 2015 - Asterix Group LLC

Preparation and updating of client base Implementation of personal sales plans Search for new customers (cold calls, business meetings, visitings of exhibition and logistics forums) Participation and victory in tenders Organization of export / import operations Training new employees



EDUCATION

GOIT ACADEMY

IT BOOTCAMP FRONT-END
Dec 2019 - till now

KYIV NATIONAL ECONOMIC UNIVERSITY NAMED AFTER VADYM HETMAN

MASTER OF MANAGEMENT 2008 - 2013



LANGUAGES





HOBBIES

TRAVEL
MUSIC
SPORT
HEALTHY LIFESTYLE